Finding Aid for Michigan Organization for Human Rights Records 1970-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Robert Lundy (Legislation Officer) Files 1974-1994
  - MOHR Files
    - Executive Director Search 1987 (Box 11)
    - Federal Gay Rights Issues 1980, undated (Box 11)
    - Financial Statements 1980-1985 (Box 11)
    - Founding Conferences 1974, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Gay Pride Parade
      - 1989 (Box 11)
      - 1990 (Box 11)
    - "History," (Box 11)
      include undated Photograph
    - Human Sexuality Statement 1980 (Box 11)
    - Insurance Bureau Advisory Committee 1988-1990 (Box 11)
    - Lamda Reports Cable TV Show 1987, undated (Box 11)
    - Legislative Committee 1986-1987 (Box 11)
    - Legislative Officers Reports 1985-1990 (Box 11)
    - Media Ascertainment Letter undated (Box 11)
    - Nominating Committee 1979 (Box 11)
    - NOW Sexual Orientation Policy 1983, undated (Box 11)
    - Personnel Investigations
      - Kathy Sarris 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - Jeffrey Swanson 1989 (Box 12)
      - Rick Wallace 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - Policy Council 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - Political Action Committee (PAC) 1980-1984 (Box 12)
    - Political Mailings/ Positions 1980 (Box 12)
    - Raffles, Correspondence 1980-1986 (Box 12)
    - Supreme Court Bias Committee 1987-1988 (Box 12)
    - Victimless Crime 1978-1982 (Box 12)
    - "Working with the Media, Guide for Community Groups and Nonprofit Organizations," undated (Box 12)
    - WVIC Complaint 1985 (Box 12)
  - Topical Files
    - ACLU Committee on Lesbian Women and Gay Men 1978-1984 (Box 12)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on AIDS 1986 (Box 12)
    - Age Discrimination 1984 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Advocacy Grant, City of Detroit 1989 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Contact Notification 1986 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Handicap Discrimination 1986-1989 (Box 12)
    - AIDS and Healthcare 1988 (Box 12)
    - AIDS: Insurance 1985-1986 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Letter to Legislative District Co-ordinators 1986 (Box 12)
    - AIDS PSAs 1987 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Related Bills 1985-1990 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Survey of Michigan Gay Men 1989 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Sub-committee of House Public Health 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - AIDS Testing, Counseling, and Fundraising 1988 (Box 12)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor Gay Rights Ordinance 1978 (Box 12)
    - Association of Suburban People 1979-1981 (Box 12)
    - Bryant Resolution 1977-1980 (Box 12)
    - California Sexual Preference Discrimination Executive Order 1979 (Box 12)
    - Child Custody 1983-1990, undated (Box 12)
    - Civil Rights 1980-1987 (Box 12)
    - Civil Rights Restoration Act 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - Civil Service Letter 1981-1994 (Box 12)
    - Cohabitation Decriminalization Report 1980 (Box 12)
    - Demonstrations 1990 (Box 12)
    - Department of Corrections, Banned Publications 1987 (Box 12)
    - Detroit Area Gay-Lesbian Council 1981 (Box 12)
    - Detroit Civil Rights Ordinance 1979 (Box 12)
    - Detroit Human Rights Ordinance 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - District of Columbia AIDS Insurance Disapproval 1986 (Box 12)
    - District of Columbia Appropriations 1987-1989 (Box 12)
    - District of Columbia Sexual Assault Reform Bill 1981 (Box 12)
    - Domestic Partners 1983-1991 (Box 12)
    - Elliott-Larsen Civil Rights Amendments 1980 (Box 12)
    - Equal Rights Amendment 1989-1991 (Box 12)
    - Fair Employment Bills 1979-1981 (Box 12)
    - Family Protection Act 1979 (Box 12)
    - Federal Civil Rights Protection 1979-1980 (Box 12)
    - Federal Employee Protection 1980 (Box 12)
    - Federal Gay Civil Rights Bill 1982-1989 (Box 12)
    - Funeral Director Notification 1986 (Box 12)
    - Gay Charities, Legal Concerns 1978 (Box 12)
    - Gay Films on Video 1986 (Box 12)
    - Gay Legal Advocates 1979-1986 (Box 12)
    - Gay Literature 1988 (Box 12)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby 1979-1985 (Box 12)
    - Gay Rights Protection in the U. S. and Canada Survey 1980 (Box 12)
    - Harassment 1982-1986 (Box 12)
    - Hate Crimes Statistics Act 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - Helms Amendment 1987 (Box 12)
    - "Heterosexuality: Can it be Cured" Pamphlet 1977 (Box 12)
    - Immigration Bills 1985-1989 (Box 12)
    - Insurance for the Uninsured 1988-1989 (Box 12)
    - Kalamazoo Murder 1986-1987 (Box 12)
    - Lansing Area Constitutional Liberties Fund, Inc. 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Lansing City Charter 1981 (Box 12)
    - Lansing City Council Profiles 1980 (Box 12)
    - Legislation on Gay Telephone Listings 1985 (Box 12)
    - Lobby Day 1987 (Box 12)
    - McDonald Amendment 1977-1981 (Box 12)
    - Marital Status 1975-1984 (Box 12)
    - Michigan Education Association 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Lesbians Health Survey 1990 (Box 13)
    - Military 1984-1989 (Box 13)
    - National Endowment for the Arts Appropriations 1989 (Box 13)
    - National Gay Task Force 1975-1985 (Box 13)
    - NOW Michigan Conference 1980 (Box 13)
    - Ohio Gay Rights Coalition (OGRC) 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Oregon Report of the Task Force on Sexual Preference 1978 (Box 13)
    - People's Campaign for Choice 1987 (Box 13)
    - Police Training, Chicago Police Department 1980-1982 (Box 13)
    - Pornography Legislation 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - Post-SOAP Committee 1981 (Box 13)
    - Rental Insurance 1981 (Box 13)
    - Seropositivity Reporting 1986 (Box 13)
    - Sex Education 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Sex Offender Registration 1981-1994 (Box 13)
    - Sexual Orientation and Affectional Preference (SOAP) Report (Box 13)
    - Sexual Orientation Employment Discrimination 1984, undated (Box 13)
    - Sexual Identity 1981-1983 (Box 13)
    - Women's Assembly 1982 (Box 13)
    - Writing to Congress undated
- Robert Lundy (Legislation Officer) Later Files 1970-1995
  This series of Lundy files contains materials kept separate from previous accessions perhaps because they represented continuing working papers. Included are additional files on legislation and local ordinances of concern to the gay/lesbian community and miscellaneous topical files mainly concerning AIDS. There is obviously some overlap of dating and subject between this series and the previous Lundy files.
  - Legislation and Ordinances
    - AIDS Bills 1985-1987 (Box 14)
    - Civil Service and Sexual Orientation in the State of Michigan 1981-1995 (Box 14)
    - Criminal Code Sex Laws (H.B. 4842) 1976-1986 (Box 14)
    - East Lansing Civil Rights Ordinance 1982-1986 (Box 14)
    - Elliot-Larsen Civil Rights Act (H.B. 5000)
      - Bill Draft and Summary 1982-1988 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence 1981-1985 (Box 14)
      - Support
        - Corporate Support 1975-1980 (Box 14)
        - Labor Union Support 1983 (Box 14)
        - Professional Organizations Support 1971-1984 (Box 14)
        - Religious Support 1980-1986 (Box 14)
        - Support Packet 1983 (Box 14)
      - Moral Majority Position Review 1984 (Box 14)
      - Legislative Concerns (Box 14)
      - District Coordinator Packet (Box 14)
      - News Articles 1983-1985 (Box 14)
      - Amendment to the Elliot Larsen Civil Rights Act (S.B. 49) 1982-1983 (Box 14)
    - Fair Housing
      - Housing Report 1983 (Box 14)
      - Fair Housing Ordinance, Jackson, MI 1985-1986 (Box 14)
      - Fair Housing Ordinances in Other Michigan Cities 1984-1989 (Box 14)
    - Family Definition for Zoning Purposes 1976-1987 (Box 14)
    - Gross Indecency Laws 1982-1989 (Box 14)
    - Group Sex Legislation (H.B. 4804 5641) 1984-1985 (Box 14)
    - Intimidation Bill (H.B. 4113) 1985-1989 (Box 14)
    - Marital Status Definition and Discrimination 1979-1989 (Box 14)
    - Obscenity Legislation 1970-1990 (Box 14)
    - Sodomy Law Challenge 1983-1990 (Box 14)
    - State Employees Retirement Act (H.B. 5603) 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Topical Files
    - AIDS/HIV
      - AIDS Appropriations 1985-1990 (Box 14)
      - AIDS/Gay Hysteria 1987 (Box 14)
      - AIDS Mailgrams 1986 (Box 14)
      - AIDS in the Workplace Articles 1985-1987 (Box 14)
      - Bulletins and Letters 1987-1989 (Box 14)
      - MOHR AIDS Taskforce 1985-1986 (Box 14)
      - News Articles 1985-1988 (Box 14)
    - Michigan State University
      - Hall Fire Incident and Complaint 1989-1990 (Box 14)
      - Non-Discrimination Policy 1981-1990 (Box 14)
    - MOHR LDC Leadership Education 1987 (Box 14)
    - MOHR Legal Affairs 1986 (Box 14)
    - Rest Stop Case 1984-1990 (Box 14)
    - Report on Sexual Orientation and Affectional Preference 1982 (Box 14)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Materials series (1986-1992; .3 linear feet and 1 oversized folder) contains mostly photographs of Gay Pride parades in Lansing and Detroit. Except for a series of 1988 photographs by Allan Glassman, the photographers are unidentified. In addition to the parade photographs are images of a Michigan Privacy Challenge demonstration in Detroit and of a fundraising dinner held in Lansing by M.O.H.R. in 1992. Among the guests of honor were the gay male weightlifting couple Rod and Bob Jackson/Paris. The posters found in this series announce meeting times for gay/lesbian organizations.
  - Photographs
    - Gay Pride Parade
      - 1986, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1988 (Allan Glassman, photographer) (Box 6)
      - 1989 (Box 6)
      - 1990, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - 1992 (Box 6)
      - Undated (Box 6)
    - Jackson-Paris Dinner 1992 (Box 6)
    - Privacy Challenge Demonstration circa 1988 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
  - Posters
    - Announcements of events, etc., 6 items (Folder Bj)
- Audiotapes, 1973-1980, 83 audiotapes reel-to-reel tapes
  The Audio Materials series (1973-1980, 3 linear feet, 83 tapes) contains reel-to-reel tapes. These tapes were part of the original accession of M.O.H.R. records and, while produced before the founding of the organization, several of those involved with the radio program Gayly Speaking went on to play significant roles in M.O.H.R. after 1977. Topical coverage includes a wide variety of political and social issues which affected the lives of lesbians and gay men in the mid- to late-1970s, as well as the cultural activities of and public service information for the Detroit-area lesbian and gay community.
  There are numerous chronological gaps in this series, with representation heaviest and most consistent for the early years of the program, 1973 to 1976. Coverage of the years 1977 to 1980 is very sketchy. The original numbering sequence of the tapes and their broadcast dates, as transcribed from the outside of individual tape boxes, have been retained as an organizational scheme. It should be noted that brackets in these dates have been transcribed as they appear on the boxes. Recording dates have been noted in the container listing when known, as have playback speeds.
  - Gayly Speaking (Radio program)
    [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Coming Out (#1), 1973 September 06, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-101-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet in tape box. Speakers identified on cue sheet are: Merrilee Melvin, Michael Owen, Dee Dee Levi, Bob Stanton, and Susan Paredes.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Sexism in Straight Society (#2), August 14, 1973, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-102-1]; mp3 file; (Not aired; recorded August 14, 1973. Tape box includes cue sheet. Speakers listed on the cue sheet are: Franz Martin, Mary Sawicki, Susan Paredes, Bob Stanton, and Don Mager.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Sexism in Gay Community (#3), 1973 August 28, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-103-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box contains attached cue sheet. Speakers on program are listed as: Merrilee Melvin, Patricia Payne, Dee Dee Levi, Don Mager, and Michael Owen)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays in Psychotherapy; Prisons (#5, #11), 1973 October 04, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-104-1]; mp3 file; (Tape contains two programs: "Gays in Psychotherapy" and "Prisons I." )
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Beauty Standard Oppression (#8), 1973 October 14, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-105-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes cue sheet from engineers. Speakers listed on cue sheet are: Susan Paredes, Harold Green, Gay Whitesides, and Dough Schultz.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gay Poetry (#9), 1973 October 09, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-106-1]; mp3 file; (Tape includes cue sheet from engineers. Speakers listed on cue sheet are: Don Mager, Pat Ansoini, Barbara Brattin, John Miseud, and Michael Owen.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gay Liberation and Socialism (#10), 1973 November 08, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-107-1]; mp3 file; (Tape includes attached cue sheet. Producers are listed as Franz Martin, Mary Sawicki, and Bob Stanton.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays in Prison (#11), 1973 November 15, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-108-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Speakers listed on cue sheet are: Michael Owen, Franz Martin, and Susan Paredes.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays in the Theatre (#15), 1973 December 13, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-109-1]; mp3 file; (Program produced by Don Mager with talent from Don Mager, Patricia Payne, and John Mifsud.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays in Prison II (#16), 1973 December 20, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-110-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes attached cue sheet. Talent listed on cue sheet is: Mike Owen, Franz Martin, and Sue Parades.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Rural Gays (#18), 1974 January 03, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-111-1]; mp3 file; (Franz Martin discussing the experiences of rural gays, Josh, Barbara, Paul and others in a small New England town.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Pro Religion (#19), 1974 January 10, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-112-1]; mp3 file; ("Gays and Christianity", various speakers discussing the relationship between homosexuality and religion.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Anti Religion (#20), 1974 January 17, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-113-1]; mp3 file; (Discussing religion's traditionally negative relationship with gay culture.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Lesbian Facilities (#21), 1974 January 24, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-114-1]; mp3 file; (Discussing social and political organizations for lesbians in the Detroit area. )
      - [Part 2], [85287-SR-114-2]; mp3 file; (Content does not match description. Joel Sugarman and others discussing the "Watergate Scandal Card Game")
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gay pride Week Review (#44), 1974 July 04, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-115-1]; mp3 file; (Includes in tape box cue sheet for engineers. Cathy Courtney singing a series of Gay and Lesbian songs for Liberation. Also includes speeches from Detroit's gay pride week.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Charter (#41) June 13, 1974 June 13, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-116-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes attached sheet. Speakers included on tape are Franz Martin and Don Mager.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] WSU: Gay Liberation Front (#38), 1974 May 05, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-117-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet; speakers listed are Art and Allen. Announcements by Don Mager and engineering by Mike Owen)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Ann Arbor/American Psychiatric Association Convention Report (#37), 1974 May 17, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-118-1]; mp3 file; (Box includes attached cue sheet. Speakers listed are Michael Owen, Bob Stanton, Greg Turner and others.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Equadere (#34), 1974 May 16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-119-1]; mp3 file; (Don Mager announcing, begins with the announcement of concerts upcoming at the time and then continues with a discussion with Gay Liberation political movements.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] The Gay Liberator (#33), 1974 May 09, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-120-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Engineered and announced by Michael Owen.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays in Films (#35), May 2,1974, 1974 May 02, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-121-1]; mp3 file; (Box includes attached cue sheet. Announcers are Don Mager and Michael Owen.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Ann Arbor Mental Health Clinic (#36), 1974 April 18, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-122-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes cue sheet for recording. Announcers are Mary Sawicki, Susan Paredes, and Patty Payne.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Couples Breaking Up (#31), 1974 April 04, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-123-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Speakers include Joel Cusman, Patricia Payne. Engineered by Michael Owen. Includes pamphlet: "Gay people have in the past been prevented by the prevailing sexism from participating in the bliss of monogamy. Now, thanks to our movement, gay people are becoming couples, like everyone else.")
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Canada (#29), 1974 March 21, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-124-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet for engineers on this recording. Announcers include: Steve Shirreffs, Harold Desmarais, Jim Davies. Franz Martin is the engineer.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Social Services (#28), 1974 March 14, Audio Reel-to-Reel
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-125-1]; mp3 file; (Discussing social services available for LGBT individuals.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gay Community Center (#27), 1974 March 07, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-126-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Franz Martin is listed as the engineer.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Hustling (#23), 1974 February 07, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-127-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Franz Martin is listed as the engineer.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Ann Arbor/American Psychiatric Association I (#45), 1974 July 11, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-128-1]; mp3 file; (Tape boxes includes cue sheet. Announcers listed are Franz Martin and Michael Owen. Engineers are Michael Owen and Bob Stanton.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Ann Arbor / American Psychiatric Association II (#46), 1974 July 18, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-129-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet from the recording. Announcers are listed as: Don Mager, Bob Stanton, and Deedee Levi.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Detroit Charter and Gay Rights (#48), 1974 August 01, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-130-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet from recording. Announcer is listed as Franz Martin.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Magazine (#50), 1974 August 15, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-131-1]; mp3 file; (Includes engineer's cue sheet. Announcers are listed as Gary Gran and Mary Sawicki.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gays and Teaching (#56), 1974 September 26, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-133-1]; mp3 file; (Includes attached cue sheet. Speakers listed are: Joanne Spiro, Barry Parel, Frank Belyan, Alice Grald, and Don Mager.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Dimensions of Gayness & Aging (#62), 1974 November 07, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-134-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet for program. Speakers listed are Don Mager and engineer is Michael Owen.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Gay Health and Rape Services in Detroit, 1974 November 21, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-135-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet for radio engineers. Speakers listed on cue sheet are: Bob Stanton, Michael Owen. Producers are Chris Reynolds and Charlotte Hier.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Stereotypes (#72), 1975 January 16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-137-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet for radio program, no speakers or engineers are listed.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Record Reviews (#74), 1975 January 30, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-138-1]; mp3 file; (A show dedicated to record reviews, played by radio announcers.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Dream Work (#76), 1975 February 13, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-139-1]; mp3 file; (Dramatized readings of Kirby Congdon poems. Poems read are: "Dedication", "First epigraph", "Second Epigraph", "Motto", "Motorcycle", "The Contes", "The Racers", The Speed Track", "The Crowd Gathered", "The Interview", "Motorcycle Day", "Training Camp", "When We Asked Our Captain", "The Patriots", "We Went Up The Statue of Liberty", "The Orgy", "Jagannath", "The Happy Journey", "The Parade", "Joy Ride", "We Turned in the Wrong Direction", "The Garden Party", "The Prison", "The Battlefield", "For Generations Past", "We Started out with the Light Hearts", "When We Got Tired of Calling", "Song: Come to the Lavender Country.")
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Book Review: Sappho Was A Right-On Woman (#80), 1975 March 13, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-140-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes engineer's cue sheet. There are no listed announcers.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Male Health Concerns (#82), 1975 March 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-141-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes engineer's cue sheet. There are no listed announcers.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Review of the Journal of Homosexual Counseling Conference (#84), 1975 April 10, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-142-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes cue sheet. Speakers listed are: Ralph Blair of the Homosexual Community Counseling Centre, Don Mager and Merrilee Melvin)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Bars (#108), 1975 September 25, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-143-1]; mp3 file; (Includes cue sheet for WDET-FM inside tape box. Speakers listed are Turner, Fournier, Ryse, and Farber.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Allen Spears & Rural Gays (#94), 1975 June 19, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-144-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes cue sheet. No speakers listed, engineers are Bob Stanton and Greg Turner.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Coming Out II (#102), 1975 August 14, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 3/4 ips
      - [Part 1], [85287-SR-145-1]; mp3 file; (Tape box includes cue sheet for engineers. No speakers listed.)
    - [Gayly Speaking Radio Program:] Poetry of Jeff Sarrasson (#98), 1975 July 17, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch